{
    "subject": "Y\u0131lmaz_G\u00fcney",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Yol",
    "human_readable": "Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney created Yol.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7170557379722595,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5924968123435974,
            "question": "Who created the film 'Yol'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49983465671539307,
            "question": "Is Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37403637170791626,
            "question": "What year was 'Yol' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28891056776046753,
            "question": "Has Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney won any awards for his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2796088755130768,
            "question": "What other films has Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24401156604290009,
            "question": "What are some of the themes explored in 'Yol'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21168556809425354,
            "question": "Where was the film 'Yol' set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18700586259365082,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Yol'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1710812747478485,
            "question": "What impact did 'Yol' have on Turkish cinema?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney created Yol.",
            "html": "yago_6536_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'Yol'?",
            "html": "yago_6536_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the film 'Yol' set?",
            "html": "yago_6536_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the themes explored in 'Yol'?",
            "html": "yago_6536_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6536_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6536_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6536_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6536_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6536_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6536_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6536_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6536_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6536_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6536_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney created Yol. The documents mention Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney as the writer and director of Yol, and also mention that he was imprisoned by Turkey's military junta while writing the film, and that he ultimately finished the film after escaping prison and going into exile."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney and his film \"Yol,\" including that he was the creator or writer of the film. Therefore, the statement \"Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney created Yol\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}